Guide to the Behind the Veil: Documenting African-American Life in the Jim Crow South Records, 1940-1997 and undated, bulk 1993-1997 RL.00170
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Use Tapes Series (UT), 1993-1997 [RESTRICTED], 14 boxes
  - Charlotte, N.C. and Environs
    - Yongue, William, Jr. (Box UT3 Tray D)
  - Durham, N.C. and Environs
    - Atwater, Ann (Box UT3 Tray D)
    - Blue, Ila (Box UT3 Tray D)
    - Blunt, Russell (Box UT3 Tray D)
    - Brinkley, Harriette (Box UT4 Tray A)
    - Brodie, Arthur (Box UT4 Tray A)
    - Bryant, Artelia (Box UT4 Tray A)
    - Bryant, R. (Box UT4 Tray A)
    - Butterfield, George (Box UT4 Tray A)
    - Bynum, Ernestine (Box UT4 Tray A)
    - Cherry, Willie (Box UT4 Tray A)
    - Clement, William (Box UT4 Tray A)
    - Crockett, Manuel (Box UT4 Tray A)
    - Davis, Willie, Jr. (Box UT4 Tray A)
    - Duncan, Anne (Box UT4 Tray A)
    - Edmonds, Vivian (Box UT4 Tray A)
    - Fitts, Howard, Jr. (Box UT4 Tray A)
    - Garrett, York (Box UT4 Tray A)
    - Hinton, Collins (Box UT4 Tray A)
    - Hughley, Sadie (Box UT4 Tray B)
    - Knight, Christopher (Box UT4 Tray B)
    - Lee, James (Box UT4 Tray B)
    - Livingston, Omeda (Box UT4 Tray B)
    - Lucas, Julia (Box UT4 Tray B)
    - Lyons, Theresa (Box UT4 Tray B)
    - Malone, Calvin (Box UT4 Tray B)
    - McCandies, Emily (Box UT4 Tray B)
    - McCoy, Vivian (Box UT4 Tray B)
    - McCullers, Henderson (Box UT4 Tray B)
    - McCullers, Patricia (Box UT4 Tray B)
    - Mimms, Horace (Box UT4 Tray B)
    - Moore, III, Malvin (Box UT4 Tray B)
    - Owens, Sam (Box UT4 Tray B)
    - Page, Benjamin (Box UT4 Tray B)
    - Page, Mildred (Box UT4 Tray B)
    - Quigless, Milton (Box UT4 Tray B)
    - Rivera, Alexander (Box UT4 Tray B)
    - Sanders, Easter (Box UT4 Tray B)
    - Sanders, James (Box UT4 Tray B)
    - Scarborough, George (Box UT4 Tray B)
    - Scarborough, George (Box UT4 Tray C)
    - Tapp, Peggy (Box UT4 Tray C)
    - Taylor, Jennie (Box UT4 Tray C)
    - West End Oral History Project (Box UT4 Tray C)
    - White, Clarence (Box UT4 Tray C)
    - White, Nathaniel (Box UT4 Tray C)
    - Wilson, Sandra (Box UT4 Tray C)
  - Enfield, N.C. and Environs
    - Allen, Suzie (Box UT4 Tray C)
    - Artis, Betty (Box UT4 Tray C)
    - Babcock, Annie (Box UT4 Tray C)
    - Battle, James (Box UT4 Tray C)
    - Bodie, Mary (Box UT4 Tray C)
    - Boone, Dorothy (Box UT4 Tray C)
    - Boone, Erma (Box UT4 Tray C)
    - Brantley, Leroy (Box UT4 Tray C)
    - Bricks Club (Box UT4 Tray C)
    - Brinkley, Claudia (Box UT4 Tray C)
    - Brinkley, Richard (Box UT4 Tray C)
    - Bronson, Bernice (Box UT4 Tray C)
    - Bullock, Lester (Box UT4 Tray C)
    - Cannon, Dorothy (Box UT4 Tray C)
    - Cochran, Doris (Box UT4 Tray C)
    - Cochran, Salter (Box UT4 Tray D)
    - Cofield, Mae (Box UT4 Tray D)
    - Coley, Frederick (Box UT4 Tray D)
    - Crowell, Maggie (Box UT4 Tray D)
    - Daniel, Mayonie (Box UT4 Tray D)
    - Edge, Effie (Box UT4 Tray D)
    - Edge, Richard (Box UT4 Tray D)
    - Ellis, Margaret (Box UT4 Tray D)
    - Exum, Julia (Box UT4 Tray D)
    - Farmer, Anthony (Box UT4 Tray D)
    - Farmer, Bertha (Box UT4 Tray D)
    - Fenner, Lillie (Box UT4 Tray D)
    - Foreman, Annie (Box UT4 Tray D)
    - Forney, Myrtle (Box UT4 Tray D)
    - Francis, Eddie (Box UT4 Tray D)
    - Francis, Eddie, Jr. (Box UT4 Tray D)
    - Francis, Eullia (Box UT4 Tray D)
    - Grant, Florenza (Box UT4 Tray D)
    - Grant, Gary (Box UT4 Tray D)
    - Grant, Matthew (Box UT4 Tray D)
    - Grant, Richard (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Harvey, Theresa (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Hedgepath, Clarence (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Hinton, Katherine (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Hunter, Nancy (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Johnson, Beaulah (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Johnson, Lucille (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Johnson, Ruth (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Johnson, Jack William (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Kea, Gladys (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Lee, Katherine (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Lee, Richard (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Leonard, Walter (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Lowe, Daisy (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Lowe, Willie (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Lynch, Georgia (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Lynch, Orator (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Lyon, David (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Lyons, Celestine (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Mallary, Lillian (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Mallory, Dezell (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Mann, Effie (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Marable, Azree (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - McWilliams, Ada (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Moore, Fred (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Moore, Mildred (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Morrow, Katherine (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Pearce, Mildred (Box UT5 Tray A)
    - Pelerson, Deatherine (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Pittman, Emerson (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Plummer, Vera (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Powell, Clarence (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Powell, Cocolua (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Powell, Willie (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Powell, Willie (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Reynolds, Pam (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Rogers, Mary (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Ruel, Solomon (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Russel, Elvenia (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Scott, Jasper (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Scott, Louise (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Smith, Cassie (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Smith, Lillie (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Spence, Vivian (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Thompson, Addie (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Thorne, Annie (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Tillery, Roy (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Tllery Community Center (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Valentine, Gracie (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Ward, Willie (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Weathersbee, Susie (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Whitaker, Mildred (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Whitehead, Lossie (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Wilkens, Evelyn (Box UT5 Tray B)
    - Williams, Lola (Box UT5 Tray C)
    - Wills, Almyra (Box UT5 Tray C)
    - Wills, Hubert (Box UT5 Tray C)
  - James City Historical Society
    - Boyd, Aaron (Box UT5 Tray C)
    - Clemmons, Ernestine (Box UT5 Tray C)
    - Gavin, Annie (Box UT5 Tray C)
    - Hill, Pleasant (Box UT5 Tray C)
    - Spivey, Bill (Box UT5 Tray C)
    - Spivey, Dorothy (Box UT5 Tray C)
  - LeFlore Co., Miss. and Environs
    - Alexander, Essie (Box UT5 Tray C)
    - Allen, Lou (Box UT5 Tray C)
    - Automon, Sarah (Box UT5 Tray C)
    - Bailey, George (Box UT5 Tray C)
    - Barber, Corean (Box UT5 Tray C)
    - Bays, Georgia (Box UT5 Tray C)
    - Bowie, Eura (Box UT5 Tray C)
    - Brown, Jackson (Box UT5 Tray C)
    - Bynum, Rosie (Box UT5 Tray C)
    - Carthan, Eddie (Box UT5 Tray C)
    - Clayborn, Arthur, Jr. (Box UT5 Tray C)
    - Conley, Annie (Box UT5 Tray C)
    - Davis, Arnette (Box UT5 Tray C)
    - Davis, William (Box UT5 Tray C)
    - Ewing, Alice (Box UT5 Tray C)
    - Federick, Booker (Box UT5 Tray D)
    - Flemming, Cora (Box UT5 Tray D)
    - Gibson, O. (Box UT5 Tray D)
    - Giles, Alice (Box UT5 Tray D)
    - Green, Ara (Box UT5 Tray D)
    - Gulledge, Lucinda (Box UT5 Tray D)
    - Hammond, Sadie (Box UT5 Tray D)
    - Howard, Irene (Box UT5 Tray D)
    - Ingram, James (Box UT5 Tray D)
    - Jackson, Ruthie (Box UT5 Tray D)
    - Johnson, John (Box UT5 Tray D)
    - Johnson, Mandie (Box UT5 Tray D)
    - Jones, Johnny (Box UT5 Tray D)
    - Lacy, Frank (Box UT5 Tray D)
    - Leach, Herman (Box UT5 Tray D)
    - Lindsey, Robert (Box UT5 Tray D)
    - Livingston, Daisy (Box UT5 Tray D)
    - Love, Hettie (Box UT5 Tray D)
    - Lucas, Maurice (Box UT5 Tray D)
    - Malone, Ruth (Box UT5 Tray D)
    - Martin, Virginia (Box UT5 Tray D)
    - Matthews, David (Box UT5 Tray D)
    - Matthews, John (Box UT5 Tray D)
    - McCaskill, Willie (Box UT5 Tray D)
    - McDonald, Nathan (Box UT5 Tray D)
    - Moore, Georgia (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Payne, Bertha (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Payne, Jessie, Jr. (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Peyton, A. (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Pitts, Elizabeth (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Reed, Willie (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Robinson, Cathon (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Robinson, James (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Robinson, Juvernia (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Rolling, Susie (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Rose, Richard (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Russell, Erma (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Sanders, Rosie (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Scott, Charles (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Scott, H. (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Sculark, Walter (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Simmons, Hattie (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Simms, Ruth (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Sims, Maggie (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Stewart, Jessie (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Stewart, Lillie (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Stewart, William (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Taylor, Julia (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Taylor, Laura (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Taylor, Lola (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Ward, Alma (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Washington, Genora (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Washington, Willie (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - Weston, Minnie (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - White, Bernice (Box UT6 Tray A)
    - White, Dorsey (Box UT6 Tray B)
    - Wicks, David (Box UT6 Tray B)
    - Williams, H. (Box UT6 Tray B)
    - Williams, R. (Box UT6 Tray B)
    - Williams, Ruby (Box UT6 Tray B)
    - Young, Chris, Sr. (Box UT6 Tray B)
  - Memphis, Tenn. and Environs
    - Ateman, Ada (Box UT6 Tray B)
    - Ballard, Lozell (Box UT6 Tray B)
    - Bates, Evelyn (Box UT6 Tray B)
    - Bond, Noah (Box UT6 Tray B)
    - Bond, Noah[et. al.] (Box UT6 Tray B)
    - Boyd, LeRoy (Box UT6 Tray B)
    - Bradley, James (Box UT6 Tray B)
    - Bragg, Savy (Box UT6 Tray B)
    - Branch, Lanetha (Box UT6 Tray B)
    - Brandon, Grace (Box UT6 Tray B)
    - Broome, Willie (Box UT6 Tray B)
    - Brown, Allen, Jr. (Box UT6 Tray B)
    - Brown, Lillie (Box UT6 Tray B)
    - Bryant, Susie (Box UT6 Tray B)
    - Buggs, Dorothy (Box UT6 Tray B)
    - Butler, Willie (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Chalmers, Artherene (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Conley, Oatie (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Cooper, Barbara (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Cooper, John (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Crivens, Hortense (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Cross, Blondale (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Cummings, Mattie (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Davis, Essie (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Davis, Matthew (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Edmond, Margarette (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Edwards, Mack (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Farris, Elizabeth (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Fitzgerald, Mae (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Forest, Earl (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Fort, Marie (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Gilliland, Jessie (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Gladney, Martha (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Golden, Addie (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Griffin, Lovie (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Harrell, Willie (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Hill, Lutisha (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Hunt, Edgar (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Hunt, Euless (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Jenkins, Henrene (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Johnson, Agnes (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Johnson, Elnora (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Johnson, Harry (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Johnson, Helen (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Johnson, JoAnn (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Johnson, Ralph (Box UT6 Tray C)
    - Jones, Amy (Box UT6 Tray D)
    - Jones, Andrenetta (Box UT6 Tray D)
    - Jones, Charles (Box UT6 Tray D)
    - Jones, Johnny (Box UT6 Tray D)
    - Jones, Merlin (Box UT6 Tray D)
    - Jones, Otha B. Strong (Box UT6 Tray D)
    - Jordan, John (Box UT6 Tray D)
    - Kirkon, Lillie (Box UT6 Tray D)
    - Lampkins, Roosevelt (Box UT6 Tray D)
    - Laws, Irene (Box UT6 Tray D)
    - Lawson, Mary (Box UT6 Tray D)
    - Leachman, Ida (Box UT6 Tray D)
    - Lee, Alversa (Box UT6 Tray D)
    - Lewis, Charles (Box UT6 Tray D)
    - Lewis, Charles [et. al.] (Box UT6 Tray D)
    - Lewis, Lenora (Box UT6 Tray D)
    - Lewis, Lucille (Box UT6 Tray D)
    - Lindsey, James (Box UT6 Tray D)
    - Malden, Rosa (Box UT6 Tray D)
    - Mayweather, Hortense (Box UT6 Tray D)
    - McDowell, Earline (Box UT6 Tray D)
    - McGee, Hazel (Box UT6 Tray D)
    - McGhee, Hazel (Box UT6 Tray D)
    - McKinley, Lucille (Box UT6 Tray D)
    - McKinley, Melvina (Box UT6 Tray D)
    - McKinley, Rebecca (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - McKinney, Frederick (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - McNeal, Mary (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - Morris, Alma (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - Murphy, Margarette (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - Neyland, Jerry (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - Ordley, Carrie (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - Ordley, Carrie (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - Pearson, Frank (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - Peterson, Ida (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - Rayburn, Lafayette (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - Richmond, Benjamin (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - Robinson, Mary (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - Rodgers, Annie (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - Rogers, Taylor (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - Scott, Joseph (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - Simons, Harry (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - Sims, Bertha (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - Sims, Constant (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - Sims, Melma (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - Smith, Georgia Maxine (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - Spencer, Robert (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - Starling, Evelyn (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - Taylor, Edmonia (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - Taylor, Evelyn (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - Thompson, Ralph (Box UT7 Tray A)
    - Tucker, Callie (Box UT7 Tray B)
    - Turner, Allegra (Box UT7 Tray B)
    - Turner, Elaine (Box UT7 Tray B)
    - Turner, Johnnie (Box UT7 Tray B)
    - Turner, Sally (Box UT7 Tray B)
    - Veazy, Rodie (Box UT7 Tray B)
    - Walton, Jessie (Box UT7 Tray B)
    - Ware, Elizabeth (Box UT7 Tray B)
    - Westbrook, Dorothy (Box UT7 Tray B)
    - Whitehead, Earline (Box UT7 Tray B)
    - Williams, Alvia (Box UT7 Tray B)
    - Williams, Elijah (Box UT7 Tray B)
    - Williams, Percy (Box UT7 Tray B)
    - Wilson, Emogene (Box UT7 Tray B)
    - Withers, Ernest (Box UT7 Tray B)
    - Woods, Earnest (Box UT7 Tray B)
    - Yahweh, Abdul (Box UT7 Tray B)
  - Mid-Michigan
    - Birden, Charles, Sr. (Box UT7 Tray B)
  - Muhlenberg Co., Ky. and Environs
    (This box also includes a videotape, "Muhlenberg Co., Ky., July 1995")
    - Cartwright, Mabel (Box UT7 Tray B)
    - Dulin, Mary (Box UT7 Tray B)
    - Eaves, Elcie (Box UT7 Tray B)
    - Eaves, James (Box UT7 Tray C)
    - Ellis, Wilodean (Box UT7 Tray C)
    - Gilmore, Sydney, Jr. (Box UT7 Tray C)
    - Goins, Mallie (Box UT7 Tray C)
    - Harris, Carrie (Box UT7 Tray C)
    - Horton, Aldrich (Box UT7 Tray C)
    - Lovan, Al (Box UT7 Tray C)
    - Martin, Dorothy (Box UT7 Tray C)
    - McClellan, Arthur (Box UT7 Tray C)
    - Smith, Leslie (Box UT7 Tray C)
    - Stafford, Carrie (Box UT7 Tray C)
    - Stafford, Willie (Box UT7 Tray C)
  - New Bern, N.C. and Environs
    - Adams, Eva (Box UT7 Tray C)
    - Attmore, Arlestus (Box UT7 Tray C)
    - Barrett, Mamie (Box UT7 Tray C)
    - Becton-Fleming, Velma (Box UT7 Tray C)
    - Bell, Rhem (Box UT7 Tray C)
    - Best, Hayward (Box UT7 Tray C)
    - Best, Stephen (Box UT7 Tray C)
    - Bland, Carolyn (Box UT7 Tray C)
    - Bland, James (Box UT7 Tray C)
    - Booker, Wallace (Box UT7 Tray C)
    - Boyd, Aaron (Box UT7 Tray C)
    - Brown, Alfreda (Box UT7 Tray C)
    - Bryan, Dorothy (Box UT7 Tray C)
    - Bryan, Samuel (Box UT7 Tray D)
    - Bryant, Arabelle (Box UT7 Tray D)
    - Campbell, Emeler (Box UT7 Tray D)
    - Campbell, Sarah (Box UT7 Tray D)
    - Carter, Dorcas (Box UT7 Tray D)
    - Clemmons, Ernestine (Box UT7 Tray D)
    - Collins, Alfreda (Box UT7 Tray D)
    - Daniels, Dolletha (Box UT7 Tray D)
    - Davis, Rebecca (Box UT7 Tray D)
    - Dent, Mary (Box UT7 Tray D)
    - Dillahunt, Leamon (Box UT7 Tray D)
    - Donaldson, Annie (Box UT7 Tray D)
    - Donlap, Nettie (Box UT7 Tray D)
    - Downing, Myrtle (Box UT7 Tray D)
    - Dudley, Lucy (Box UT7 Tray D)
    - Dunson, Helen (Box UT7 Tray D)
    - Evans, Narcissus (Box UT7 Tray D)
    - Forbes, Rowene (Box UT7 Tray D)
    - Franklin, William (Box UT7 Tray D)
    - Gavin, Annie (Box UT7 Tray D)
    - George, Grace (Box UT7 Tray D)
    - Gramtham, Rosa (Box UT7 Tray D)
    - Harding, James (Box UT7 Tray D)
    - Harris, Clayton (Box UT7 Tray D)
    - Hayes, James (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - Hickman, Willie (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - Jones, Frances (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - Joyner, Luvenia (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - Kelsey, Christine (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - League, Mary (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - Lewis, Astor (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - Lewis, James (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - Lewis, Marion (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - Lewis, Rosetta (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - Lewis, Ruth (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - McCoy, Lucinda (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - Moore, Catherine (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - Moore, George (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - Morgan, Leander (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - Moye, John (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - Payne, Velma (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - Perry, Mary (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - Pickens, Lucille (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - Roberts, Mary (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - Ryder, Loretta (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - Ryder, Naomi (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - Simmons, Ruth (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - Spicer, Bessie (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - Stone, Mary (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - Strong, Andrew (Box UT8 Tray A)
    - Sutton, Georgia (Box UT8 Tray B)
    - Wade, Harriet (Box UT8 Tray B)
    - White, Clay (Box UT8 Tray B)
    - White, Mary (Box UT8 Tray B)
    - White, Ronald (Box UT8 Tray B)
    - Whitfield, Emma (Box UT8 Tray B)
    - Williams, Janie (Box UT8 Tray B)
    - Wordlaw, Clarita (Box UT8 Tray B)
  - New Iberia, La. and Environs
    - Allen, JoAnn (Box UT8 Tray B)
    - Auguster, Edran (Box UT8 Tray B)
    - Bernard, Lucille (Box UT8 Tray B)
    - Bijou, Hattie (Box UT8 Tray B)
    - Bijou, Prosper (Box UT8 Tray B)
    - Blaise, Edward (Box UT8 Tray B)
    - Bonds, Edward (Box UT8 Tray B)
    - Boutte, Lester (Box UT8 Tray B)
    - Broussard,Anderson (Box UT8 Tray B)
    - Carson, Martha (Box UT8 Tray B)
    - Chassion, Jessie (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Cobb, Doris (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Coleman, Baron (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Crofton, Clarence (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Drexler, Clarence (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Drexler, Ruby (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Durall, Melvenia (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Gabriel, Audrey (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Gibson, Cora (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Gibson, Ivory (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Granger, Joseph (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Hadnott, Frances (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Hadnott, Louie (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Harding, William (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Henderson, John (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Henderson, James, Sr. (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Henry, Joseph (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Hills, Erline (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Jack, Georgiana (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Jackson, Cora (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Jackson, Cyrus (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - James, Herman (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Jean-Batiste, Maude (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Jones, Josephine (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Jones, Mertha (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Jones, Mertha (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Joseph, Arthur (Box UT8 Tray C)
    - Joseph, Rose (Box UT8 Tray D)
    - Knatt, Alvin (Box UT8 Tray D)
    - Knatt, Clement (Box UT8 Tray D)
    - Knatt, Foreman (Box UT8 Tray D)
    - Knatt, Willia (Box UT8 Tray D)
    - Landry, Agnes (Box UT8 Tray D)
    - LeDee, Mary (Box UT8 Tray D)
    - Livingston, Alice (Box UT8 Tray D)
    - Manuel, Armstong (Box UT8 Tray D)
    - Manuel, Beulah (Box UT8 Tray D)
    - Mathews, Irene (Box UT8 Tray D)
    - Metz, Ernest (Box UT8 Tray D)
    - Metz, Ernest (Box UT8 Tray D)
    - Miller, Sylvania (Box UT8 Tray D)
    - Miller, Taylor (Box UT8 Tray D)
    - Mitchell, Maizel (Box UT8 Tray D)
    - Moore, Albert, Sr. (Box UT8 Tray D)
    - Noah, Esther (Box UT8 Tray D)
    - Noah, Joseph (Box UT8 Tray D)
    - Polk, Edith (Box UT8 Tray D)
    - Polk, Matthew (Box UT8 Tray D)
    - Polk, Washington (Box UT9 Tray A)
    - Raggette, Alfred (Box UT9 Tray A)
    - Raymond, Albert (Box UT9 Tray A)
    - Rochelle, Wendy (Box UT9 Tray A)
    - Russell, James, Sr. (Box UT9 Tray A)
    - Sigue, Altemus, Jr. (Box UT9 Tray A)
    - Smith, Alfred (Box UT9 Tray A)
    - Sutton, Vrginia (Box UT9 Tray A)
    - Thompson, William, Jr. (Box UT9 Tray A)
    - Thompson, Joe, Sr. (Box UT9 Tray A)
    - Vital, Otto (Box UT9 Tray A)
    - Volter, John (Box UT9 Tray A)
    - Volter, Victoria (Box UT9 Tray A)
    - Williams, Grady (Box UT9 Tray A)
    - Zepherin, William (Box UT9 Tray A)
  - New Orleans, La. and Environs
    - Aaron, Dolores (Box UT9 Tray A)
    - Alexander, Avery (Box UT9 Tray A)
    - Allen, Philomene (Box UT9 Tray B)
    - Bartholomew, Norman (Box UT9 Tray B)
    - Bashful, Emmett (Box UT9 Tray B)
    - Battiste, Harold (Box UT9 Tray B)
    - Beslin, Joseph (Box UT9 Tray B)
    - Borders, Florence (Box UT9 Tray B)
    - Boucree, John (Box UT9 Tray B)
    - Bouise, Louise (Box UT9 Tray B)
    - Brown, Eula (Box UT9 Tray B)
    - Brumfield, Eddie (Box UT9 Tray B)
    - Butler, Mary (Box UT9 Tray B)
    - Caitone, Beverly (Box UT9 Tray B)
    - Cappie, Herbert (Box UT9 Tray B)
    - Cappie, Ruth (Box UT9 Tray B)
    - Charles, Millie (Box UT9 Tray B)
    - Cheri, Emmett (Box UT9 Tray B)
    - Clem, Hugh (Box UT9 Tray B)
    - Cook, Olivia (Box UT9 Tray C)
    - Dave, Peter, Jr. (Box UT9 Tray C)
    - Davillier, Brenda (Box UT9 Tray C)
    - Davis, Mary (Box UT9 Tray C)
    - Dejan, Harold (Box UT9 Tray C)
    - Despenza, William (Box UT9 Tray C)
    - Dunbar, Viola (Box UT9 Tray C)
    - Elloie, Pealie (Box UT9 Tray C)
    - Franklin, Louise (Box UT9 Tray C)
    - Gardner, Albert, Jr. (Box UT9 Tray C)
    - Goods, Laura (Box UT9 Tray C)
    - Gourrier, Michael (Box UT9 Tray C)
    - Hill, Veronica (Box UT9 Tray C)
    - Honore, Alcee (Box UT9 Tray C)
    - Hunter, Johnny (Box UT9 Tray C)
    - Jackson, Olga (Box UT9 Tray C)
    - Jenkins, Julius (Box UT9 Tray C)
    - Johnson, Mary (Box UT9 Tray C)
    - Jordan, Edward (Box UT9 Tray C)
    - Joseph, Irvin (Box UT9 Tray C)
    - Kerry, Augusta (Box UT9 Tray C)
    - Ledoux, Jerome (Box UT9 Tray D)
    - Lee, Silas (Box UT9 Tray D)
    - Lundy, Veora (Box UT9 Tray D)
    - Lyons, Alma (Box UT9 Tray D)
    - Lyons, Marcus (Box UT9 Tray D)
    - Macdonald, Bessie (Box UT9 Tray D)
    - Merrick, Olga (Box UT9 Tray D)
    - Moore, Hazel (Box UT9 Tray D)
    - Morial, Francis (Box UT9 Tray D)
    - Morris, Jeff, Jr. (Box UT9 Tray D)
    - Mouton, Jessie (Box UT9 Tray D)
    - Oselen, Maude (Box UT9 Tray D)
    - Pajeaud, Marjorie (Box UT9 Tray D)
    - Parker, Quillie (Box UT9 Tray D)
    - Perry, Lillian (Box UT9 Tray D)
    - Preston, Mary (Box UT9 Tray D)
    - Prevost, Maurice (Box UT9 Tray D)
    - Quant, Brenda (Box UT9 Tray D)
    - Reed, Clarita (Box UT9 Tray D)
    - Rhone, Archie (Box UT9 Tray D)
    - Robertson, Audrey (Box UT9 Tray D)
    - Robertson, Dolores (Box UT10 Tray A)
    - Robinson, Wilde (Box UT10 Tray A)
    - Rousseve, Evelyn (Box UT10 Tray A)
    - Rousseve, Mildred (Box UT10 Tray A)
    - Smith, Charles (Box UT10 Tray A)
    - Smith, Germaine (Box UT10 Tray A)
    - Smith, Helen (Box UT10 Tray A)
    - Spencer, Emanuella (Box UT10 Tray A)
    - St. Julien, Aline (Box UT10 Tray A)
    - Stanley, Beatrice (Box UT10 Tray A)
    - Thomas, George, Jr. (Box UT10 Tray A)
    - Williams, Everett (Box UT10 Tray A)
  - Norfolk, Va. and Environs
    - Abbyss, Mary (Box UT10 Tray A)
    - Bass, Lena (Box UT10 Tray A)
    - Bell, Barbera (Box UT10 Tray A)
    - Benton, Annie (Box UT10 Tray A)
    - Boone, Geraldine (Box UT10 Tray A)
    - Bradley, Dolores (Box UT10 Tray A)
    - Branchcomb, Flossie (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Brandon, Elroy (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Brickers, Alease (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Brown, John (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Brown, Shirley (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Cherry, Olivia (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Coker, William (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Crudup, Henrietta (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Dabney, Lena (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Downing, Horace (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Downing, Horace (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Dozier, Essie (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Dozier, Essie (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Edmonds, Marian (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Edwards, Pearly (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Forrest, Kate (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Foster, John (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Gordon, Margaret (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Goss, Jocelyn (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Gowens, Madeline (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Gray, Cecille (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Grimstead, Lucille (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Grimstead, Sarah (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Hall, Doris (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Hayslette, Elnora (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Johnson, Harvey (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Johnson, Jessie (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Lawson, Arthur (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Lawson, Leon (Box UT10 Tray B)
    - Linyear, Josephine (Box UT10 Tray C)
    - Linyear, William (Box UT10 Tray C)